♫ I didn't get picked ♫
♫ I'm 18 now ♫
♫ No mo' games for me now ♫
♫ Unh, unh, suck it ♫
♫ Move Move ♫
♫ Move It's time to rock the house ? ♫
♫ Move It's time to rock, rock, rock ♫
♫ Move It's time to rock the house ♫
♫ Move It's time to rock the house... ♫
♫ Rock, rock ♫
♫ Feel the motion as the mood changes ♫
♫ Round and round just like the moon phases ♫
♫ This the part that keeps the place blazin' ♫
♫ Uh-huh Feel the vibe ♫
♫ I like it, amazing ♫
♫ We go hard, overnight ball ♫
♫ Party right, so it can't be wrong ♫
♫ My team cannot lose ♫
♫ Here to put on a show for you ♫
♫ It's time to rock the house ♫
♫ Move It's time to rock the house ♫
♫ Move It's time to rock, rock, rock ♫
♫ Move, move It's time to rock, rock ♫
♫ Yeah Go ♫
♫ Oh! Oh! Oh! Go ♫
♫ La, la la la... ♫
♫ Please shut your eyes ♫
♫ Your life is fading out ♫
♫ Yes, you are going to die ♫
♫ And worms will fill your mouth ♫
♫ Just check right now ♫
♫ The worms are all about ♫
♫ Guh-dunh-goh ♫
♫ Ooh, baby ♫
♫ You know what we're gonna do ♫
♫ It's time for makin' love ♫
♫ Just me and you ♫
♫ Oh, baby ♫
♫ You know what we came to do ♫
♫ Aww. Kantmiss. It's time for makin' love ♫
♫ Just me and you Like that ♫
♫ 'Cause now that you're here ♫
♫ I'm gonna... ♫
♫ Oh, baby Yeah ♫
♫ District 12! You know what we're gonna do ♫
♫ That's it! It's time for makin' love ♫
♫ Just me and you Ahh. ♫
♫ Whoa, oh, whoa ♫
♫ Move ♫
♫ Move... ♫
♫ Move It's time to rock the house ♫
♫ It's time to rock the house... ♫
♫ It's time to rock the house Move... ♫
♫ Move It's time to rock the house... ♫
♫ Boom, chika, boom, chika ♫
♫ Boom, chika, boom, boom, chika be ♫
♫ Be, chika, boom chik ♫
♫ Boom, chika, boom, chika ♫
♫ Boom, chika, boo... ♫
♫ It's time to rock the house... ♫
♫ It's time to rock the house ♫
♫ Move It's time to rock, rock, rock ♫
♫ ? Move It's time to rock the house ♫
♫ Move ? It's time to rock the house ♫
♫ Move ? It's time to rock, rock, rock... ♫
♫ Move ♫
♫ Move It's time to rock, rock, rock... ♫
♫ Move, move, move ♫
♫ Move ♫
Hey, Kantmiss!
I am the great and powerful...
Aah!
Dale!
Just wanted to surprise you.
You made me miss my shot.
Ow.
Son of a bitch! My back!
Look what I got.
Is it real?
Ohh! Psych!
It's gag bread!
Look at you.
Right.
You know...
we could run away from here.
We could live someplace else.
Like where?
Anywhere that's better than here.
Darfur. Syria.
New Jersey.
Dale, that's...that's romantic and all...
but I can't leave my sister.
I can't leave either.
My dear, old grandma depends on me to feed her.
God, I am never having kids.
I mean, how can you raise a child
in a world where they televise
all of life's misery and inhumanity and then pass it off
as some sort of twisted entertainment?
"The Hunger Games."
"16 and Pregnant."
Good morning,
hungry citizens of District 12.
In today's news, we still have no food,
and the weather will be shitty.
Oh, and don't forget,
today is the Gathering Ceremony,
so, parents, please bring your beloved children
to the square for a random death lottery.
Thank you.
I heard that some kids are so afraid
of getting picked for the Games
that they'll actually try to get disqualified
by injuring or maiming themselves.
That's an urban legend.
Uhh!
Get in line.
Oh, come on, bitch.
Ipso facto p...
Your movie franchise is over.
Get back in line.
Bloody dick.
Hey, no talking.
Keep it moving.
I gotta find my sister.
Good luck.
Petunia. Kantmiss.
Hey, Mom.
I'm scared, Kantmiss. I'm scared.
Hey, hey, don't be. I got you this.
It's the most courageous bird that there is...
a chicken.
When you wear this, nothing bad can happen to you.
Shh. Shh. No, don't cry.
You're gonna be fine, okay?
I promise.
Keep moving.
Line up!
Girls on the right. Boys on the left!
Welcome to the 75th annual Starving Games.
Oh. Oh! Ohh!
Hey. Ohh!
But that was my sausage!
And now a video from our esteemed leader,
President Snowballs.
He once killed his own mother...
because she forgot to cut the crust off his PB&J.
His only Facebook friend is Mel Gibson.
He has an online blog
that gives away the endings of movies
without ever using the disclaimer "spoiler alert."
What? He is...
the most terrible man in the world.
I don't always like beer,
but when I want one, I choose Tres Equis.
Tastes like piss water.
Aah!
Every year, I make you watch this video,
because, well, you're dumb.
People forget how in the past
shit really hit the fan.
Corporations got too big, and people lost trust.
They staged sit-ins. They rioted.
You elected Lady Gaga as President
and her running mate Nicki Minaj.
That's why we wear these kooky clothes now
and have bizarre hairdos.
Then I took over
and separated the country into districts
so that stupid shit never happened again.
Aah!
You've proven that democracy doesn't work,
and I'm here, in my sixth self-proclaimed term,
to ensure that all free will is expunged,
never to rear its ugly head again.
Yes, that brings us to today.
Just to prove what a sick, sadistic prick I am
and how you have no control...
and admittedly after watching "The Running Man"
and the Japanese cult hit "Battle Royale,"
I came up with the Starving Games.
Two kids from each district are selected
to play a game to the death with only one survivor.
The winner is to be showered with a bounty,
including an old ham...
Oh, I love old ham.
this coupon to Subway...
buy any foot-long for a six-inch price...
and...
a partially eaten pickle.
So happy Starving Games,
and may the odds be never in your favor.
A President Snowballs production.
Now let the gathering begin! Ahem.
Hugh Janus.
Hmm?
No? Yeah. All right.
I'll pick again. Heh.
Phil Mahooters.
Please, Phil Mahooters?
Dean Gullberry.
Everyone look around.
Check behind you for a Dean Gullberry.
This is being televised around the country!
You won't be laughing
when two of you are picked and thrown into the arena
for your most certain deaths.
Ahem.
It's okay.
Petunia Evershot.
Whoo!
Yes! Yes!
I didn't get picked.
Hoo-whoo!
Hoo! Whoo! Yeah!
Whoo! Come on! Gimme some.
Yeah. One more. Oh! Whew.
But I got picked.
Petunia, I am so sorry.
Petunia, no. Not fair.
Do not give me those puppy-dog eyes.
I volunteer!
Oh.
I volunteer for the Starving Games!
Thanks, big sis.
Oh! If you never make it back from the Games,
can I eat your pet hamster?
What?
Come, dear.
Now let's pick a boy to join you in the games.
I volunteer also!
Who said that?
I did.
I'm Peter Malarkey.
Oh.
Hey, Kantmiss.
I volunteered because I like you,
a lot, and I... I'm sorry.
Do I know you?
Um...
I'm...I'm the baker's son.
I once fed you when you were hungry.
Oh, right.
You gave me that walnut bread.
Yeah.
I have a severe nut allergy,
and I almost died.
Let's hear it for our contestants!
And don't forget to tune in to the Starving Games
after the season finale of "Downton Abbey."
Can't we say our goodbyes?
Of course, dear.
The Capital isn't completely inhumane.
You got 9 seconds.
Petunia! Kantmiss!
Don't worry. You're in good hands with Mom.
What's up with that Peter dude?
What?
I mean he's a total dork, right?
How much do you think he benches?
Uh...
Time's up!
Dale! Yeah?
Promise me you'll take care of Petunia!
I will, Kantmiss.
I promise.
Wait!
Later.
Shitheads.
The Nike Swoosh?
Yes, I started selling
advertising space on my face.
Your willingness to sell out and whore yourself
is the primary reason I made you head programmer.
Thank you, Mr. President.
How is the big TV show looking?
Fantastic. We've replaced Charlie Sheen with Ashton Kutcher,
and no one really seems to give a shit.
And the Starving Games?
It's gonna be a great show.
We have some very interesting contestants,
with 2 volunteers from District 12.
Volunteers.
R-O-T-F-L-O-L.
And because you made it law
that whoever doesn't watch the Games would be publicly flogged,
we're expecting record high ratings.
Well, after last years debacle,
I really had no choice.
"Celebrity Starving Games" was a lousy idea.
No one could have anticipated
that Oprah would eat all the other contestants.
I want this game to go off without a hitch.
I don't want some underdog
from a poor district to enter the Games and stir up the masses
with her archery skills and her brunette hair
fashioned into a trademark single braid,
inspiring revolt which will not only overthrows my presidency,
but also spawns a successful
four-quadrant blockbuster.
Ohh!
And I may need a new gardener.
I'm Stanley Ceaserman, and this is
"The Starving Games Countdown Show!"
Tomorrow, the Games begin,
but tonight, we're going to meet the contestants.
You'll get to know them
through their touching backstories,
where we'll manipulate you with heavily edited
home video footage and tragic testimonials.
Then, when you're emotionally attached to them,
we'll send them off to their horrific slaughter.
Let's meet our first contestant.
Going in order from District One,
he's the odds-on favorite to win this thing.
He's blond. He's Waspy.
He's the Aryan youth incarnate.
He's Marco!
Yeah!
Ahh! Yeah!
Hello, guy.
Tell us about yourself.
I'm from District One. It's a prime district.
Who are you?
I'm Cinnamon,
your stylist.
How are you holding up?
I'm scared.
I don't want to die.
Ahh. I'm here to tell you
that I believe in you.
You can win this.
I looked at your records,
and you are smarter and craftier than all of them.
Really? You think that I can win?
Yes, Patricia.
I know it.
Who's Patricia?
You're not the girl from District Three?
No, I'm from District 12.
You know, this is perfectly normal.
You seem like you strong...
And now, from District 12, Peter Malarkey.
So, Peter, tell us,
is there a special someone in your life?
Yeah.
Yeah, there is someone.
Aww. Aww.
Ohh.
Well, do tell.
The person's actually here tonight,
a person who is...
also in the Games.
In the Games with you?
Aww. Aww.
Well, go on.
Well...
it's a person I've been wanting
to get closer to for a long time.
You son of a bitch.
So...
tall,
with beautiful eyes
and a smoking hot bod, but...
you know, more than anything,
this person's got a lot of heart.
Aww. Aww.
Well, you must tell us. Who is it?
It's Marco!
Me?
Heh.
Huh? Huh?
Let's hear it for Peter.
You little shit!
I'm gonna stick a foot in your ass!
Ohh! Jeez.
What the hell was that about?
It's called building an alliance.
Haven't you ever watched "Survivor" or "Big Brother"?
Aah! When's...
When was the last time you trimmed your toenails?
Ohh.
And now, for our final contestant,
from District 12,
Kantmiss Evershot.
Whoo!
Let's take a look.
Kantmiss is the best big sister in the world.
She takes care of me. She feeds me. She clothes me.
She even reads to me.
Ever since Dad died,
Mom's been a little bummed out,
but that doesn't stop the three of us from having a whole lot of fun.
From the first time I saw Kantmiss, I knew.
I knew she was the one for me.
She's got class.
She's a real lady.
Oh, my God.
Ohh! Oh, my God.
Ohh! Ohh!
Isn't that just touching?
Aww. Aww.
Let's bring her out, shall we?
Kantmiss Evershot!
So, Kantmiss, that's quite a dress.
Give us a little spin.
Heh. Go on.
Don't be shy.
Very nice.
Oh.
Wow, I'm getting word that flames
actually ignite from the dress.
Flames?
Oh! Oh!
Oh, my God. Oh.
Oh, Aah!
Why are you clapping, you stupid?!
Aah!
I'm on fire! I'm on fire!
Let's hear it for Kantmiss, the girl on fire!
Ah! It's on fire!
It's on fire! It burns!
I'm on fire!
Good morning, sport fans,
and welcome to the 75th annual Starving Games.
I'm your host Bob Hylox,
and with me is my sidekick
and color commentator, Cleaver Williams.
Cleaver, how you doing?
Excited about today's Games?
Fantastic.
Cleaver is a past Games winner, of course.
In fact, Cleaver, why don't you tell everybody
in the district watching,
how you got that delightful nickname.
I used a meat cleaver to kill everyone.
Still got the old moves.
Hello, Siri.
Hello, Seleca.
How's it hanging, boo?
Low and to the left.
Good one.
All right. Looks like the contestants
have taken the field.
All right, Siri, cut to the field.
Say your prayers, my son, 'cause you are dead.
And the countdown has begun.
30...
29...
Oh, God. 28...
27...
Hmm?
26...
25...
24...
23...
21...
Now, it's very important
that the contestants don't move
off the silver circles before zero.
Otherwise, kablammo,
as the field is booby-trapped with explosives.
Don't need to remind me.
I went too soon, and I still can't poop right.
How 'bout that?
13...
12...
11...Huh?
What are you doing here?
We were asked to perform
at the opening ceremony.
This is the arena.
Oh, you're looking for stage two.
Oh. Thanks. Thanks.
Oops.
Wow! What a way to start the Games!
10...
9...
8...
7...
6...
5...
4...
3...
2...
1.
Siri, more blood.
Oh.
Much better.
Ooh! Ooh!
Yeah, Marco! Yeah!
Let go!
I got here first!
Yaah! Now give it to me!
No. I'm not letting go.
There is a dagger in your back!
I'm okay!
What?
It's fine.
It's fine?
Seriously? You're not letting go?
I want this backpack!
I want it. It's mine!
I'm not letting go!
That was my backpack!
What was that sound?
It's the cannon. They shoot it off
to announce whenever someone is killed.
Nice. Looks like the odds
just got better for me, then.
My balls!
Oh! That has got to hurt.
Let's see an instant replay.
My balls!
My ball...
My ball... My...My ball...
My balls!
That makes me laugh, Bob.
Get away from me!
Wow!
Who is this girl?
What district is she from?
I'm standing here in scummy District 12,
where people can't believe that Peter and Kantmiss
have actually survived the opening.
You can see the excitement is high,
as no one from this district has won in a very long time.
Yeah! Unh!
Go, Kantmiss! Whoo!
That's my girl!
Yeah!
Back to you in the studio.
I'm on TV!
Thanks, Stanley.
And how's the scoreboard looking, Cleaver?
Got a lot of people dead.
Still, lot of people alive.
Enlightening.
Oh, looks like Kantmiss is making her way
to the outer edge of the arena.
Siri, slow her down.
Ow.
Now let's get Kantmiss back to the center of the action.
Holla!
And cue the thrilling action music.
Ooh.
Hmm.
Oh, you want to play, huh? Okay.
Siri.
Yeah, what you need?
Attack her with the latest
technological weaponry we have.
Whoo-hah!
Oh, shit!
Yah! Whee hee hee!
Hee hee hee!
No.
What? What?
Orange you glad to see me?
Hey, hey, hey!
What do you get when you cross an orange
with Quentin Tarantino?
"Pulp Fiction." You get it?
Pulp.
Hey, Kantmiss,
last time I saw tits that small,
I was staring at a pair of kumquats.
Aah!
Go, Kantmiss!
Ooh,
she sure showed yo' sorry ass up!
You...You shut up, Siri. You shut up!
Shit. Don't hate the player.
You... Hate the game!
Wow! I've never seen anyone do that before.
She's badass.
Respect.
Reminds me a little bit of myself.
I'll stop now before I get too emotional.
Eat my ass!
Think you're so tough?
Well, come back from this, bitch!
Hey, guys, come on! Let's go this way!
Come on. Hurry!
Let's go!
When I see her, she's mine.
She's gotta be around here somewhere.
You sure Kantmiss came this way?
Uh, I know it.
How can we be so sure that we can trust you?
I mean, didn't you volunteer to be in the games
just so you can get closer to Kantmiss?
No.
I mean, maybe at first,
but I don't like her anymore.
Really?
Well, you know,
back in District 12, she's...
she's known as quite the whore.
Ahh.
There.
Heh.
Nice work, Peter.
Thanks.
I'm gonna bust her gut wide open.
This little princess is all mine.
Raah!
And there's Kantmiss!
Oh, no. We're gonna kill you.
Right after we eat our delicious treats.
Huh?
How can you be with them?
I don't know.
I...I guess I just...
really like them.
Th-They're so cool and popular.
I mean, I'm in the high school A/V club.
I've never been able to hang with the in crowd before.
Mmm. Stay with us.
So good.
Mmm. Oh.
Hey, they said they want to go to prom with me.
We're gonna rent a limo and everything.
Isn't that awesome?
Peter, they are just using you.
There can only be one winner of the Starving Games.
Right.
All right, Kantmiss, game over.
Glammer, you're up.
Whoo-hoo-hoo!
Oh! Looks like we got ourselves a streaker.
Happens every Game.
What a yahoo.
Get out of here, man. Get out of here!
Come back here. Come back here.
Give me that.
Nice impaling. Yeah.
He did this.
Then it did that.
Indeed, Cleaver.
And that's definitely gonna be
our Kill of the Day!
Kill of the Day!
Kill of the Day... of the Day!
Our Kill of the Day is brought to you
by BetLife insurance.
Because life is precious...
BetLife.
How are we going to kill her?
Ahem.
Uh...
why don't we just take off,
uh, go kill some other kids
and come back later?
We'll wait.
She has to come down sooner or later.
Gross.
Hey.
Shh.
Oh.
Have the bees land on their heads.
Okay. No, shh. Shh.
Those are tracker bees.
Getting stung causes serious hallucinations.
Or death.
Oh!
Ow! Ow!
Oh! My ass! Aah!
I think I just swallowed one!
Whoa.
Ooh.
Whoa. Ooh.
What...
Oh, my God. Oh!
Oh. Oh.
Whoo.
Oh.
No way.
Double rainbow.
Whoo!
Double rainbow! Ha!
Oh.
It's starting to look
like a quadruple rainbow!
Oh, my Gooood!
Yes! Yes!
Ah ha ha!
Oh, taste the rainbow.
Ooh.
Oh. Oh.
Oh. Wha?
Oh, my...
What is...
Oh.
Do not make any sudden movements.
What's wrong?
I've never seen this happen before.
What are they?
Soul keepers.
Soul keepers!
Ah! Oh, my God! Get 'em off! Get 'em off!
Get 'em off! Get 'em off!
You are not keeping my soul!
Oh! Why?
Right above your head.
No, no, no, no.
Whew.
I think I got 'em all.
Soul Keepers hold all of the souls of our ancient ancestors.
There goes my sister,
my grandma
and my drunk Aunt Sheila.
Oops.
Who are you?
We are a proud and ancient people
created by James Cameron.
I'm the king of the world!
Here.
Give me your hair.
We'll join the ends and make love,
Na'vi style.
Okay.
Ohh.
Yeah.
Oh, yes.
Kantmiss.
Kantmiss!
Yes.
Kantmiss! Kantmiss!
Kantmiss!
Are you trying to hook up with me?
What? No!
No, no, no, no. Um...
I think that I was just hallucinating.
You better not be. I'm only 12.
The way I see it, if we're gonna survive,
we should work together.
But what happens if we're the last two standing?
I won't hesitate.
This competition is kill or be killed,
and I will kill you where you stand,
dead, end of story.
Shit ain't personal,
strictly business ya dig?
Okay. Here's what I was thinking.
I could set some fires
to flush Marco and his crew out into the clearing,
and if you find a bow and arrow,
you could pick 'em off.
No, no. That's... That's a great idea,
and Marco will never see it coming.
Hello?
I'm right here.
Run! Run!
Get her!
Shit.
Totally outnumbered.
What do I do? What do I do?
Think, Kantmiss. Think.
Hemorrhoidal irritation.
Aggravate with a swift kick to the posterior.
Raah!
Low-hung scrotum. Debilitate with
concise rabbit punch to the testicular sac.
Awkward metallic orthodontic corrective device.
Snap rubber bands to create blunt force to the cranium.
Rampant adolescent acne vulgaris.
Ah.
Prescribe topical acne cream.
Pubescent boy with raging hormones.
Disarm with natural assets.
Allow to motorboat.
You're pretty.
Raah!
Hee.
You ready to die?
Not really!
I mean, kind of hoping
I could stick around for the sequel?
Huh? Huh?
Mm!
All right! We know what that sound is.
It's the end of the half.
Ah, that sucks.
I wanted to see her die.
Halftime
with the Starving Games cheerleaders,
presented by Viagra.
Eh, I like it, Siri, but it's not...
it's not popping.
Don't worry, boo. I got you.
More filthy and gratuitous T&A coming up.
Kantmiss, what an exciting first half.
Tell us what you're thinking right now.
First off, I want to thank my Lord and Savior Jesus Christ.
And, uh, I'm thinking about winning, Stanley.
I just want to win.
Bob.
Stanley, do you get a sense that Kantmiss
is aware of the frenzy she's creating?
I don't think so, Bob.
She's electrifying.
Cleaver's Electrifying Halftime Highlights.
Aah!
Take a look at what's trending right now on Twitter.
Helen in District 7 tweets, "Kantmiss gives me hope!"
And Thomas in District 11 writes,
"Kantmiss rocks, UR sooooo hot!"
And Tyrone in the District of Compton tweets,
"Yo, that ho Kantmiss is da bomb,
she's mad blowin' up in da hood, yo!"
Smiley face emoticon.
She is blowin' up,
and I had the chance to be
on the ground in Kantmiss' own district,
where Kantmiss fever is at an all-time high!
I'm here in District 12,
where everyone is going nuts.
It's the ultimate underdog Cinderella story,
and the po' folks here is eating it up,
buying up merchandise with any and everything that has to do
with Kantmiss or the Starving Games.
T-shirts, mugs,
totes, koozies
and bobbleheads.
Look at me. I'm just like Kantmiss.
Ohh!
Mis cojones.
Yes! Direct hit!
I'm gonna shoot him again.
Ai! Cheese enchilada!
Oh, that felt good.
That was a close one. Yeah.
I almost got you.
I know. I was like, "Ohh."
Take previous positions.
Game on!
Yay!
You ready to die?
Aah! Aah!
You little turd!
Hey!
Aah!
Rudy.
Sing me a lullaby.
Okay.
Not you!
Her!
Am I gonna die?
No. No, no, no.
Of course you're not gonna die.
Worms? Isn't that a little dramatic?
Damn you, Taylor Swift.
What an emotional and...
moving death, Cleaver.
It would bring a tear to my eye
if my tear ducts weren't lacerated.
Ohh. Ohh.
I'm sorry.
This is bullshit.
The Capital can't just treat us like pawns.
Yeah! Yeah!
Our life is our own,
and they can't just make us kill each other
for their own sick amusement!
Yeah! Yeah!
What do you say?
Let's riot
and overthrow this totalitarian government
once and for all!
Yeah! Yeah!
Whoo-hoo!
We take a half-pound of grade-A beef...
and top it with cheese.
Then we top it with chili...
and a hot dog and ribs
and smother it with low-cal ranch dressing.
Then we top it with a slice of pepperoni pizza,
with a sesame-seed bun.
Mmm, mmm.
Hey, uh...
are we still gonna riot?
Maybe later.
I'm too hungry now.
Then we add barbeque sauce...
tomato, onion and lettuce.
Then we add pork rinds,
Funyuns, broccoli, nacho cheese,
Spam and wings...
and ham hocks, chitlins.
Don't forget the watermelon wedge.
Top it all off with two scoops of pistachio ice cream,
and finish it with another sesame-seed bun.
The 600,000 calorie triple bypass burger.
Starbucks?
Got a free latte for it.
Kantmiss fever is causing a serious problem.
We almost had a riot.
What should we do?
Give them more.
I don't understand.
The Starving Games is a hit.
Just look at the trades.
We could finally win an Emmy.
But the show's missing one important thing.
What does every successful show need
to bring it to the next level?
I know exactly what you mean.
A love story! A lesbian love story!
Wait. Lesbian love story?
Who doesn't like to see two chicks get it on?
I know I do, big time.
But there aren't any other women
left alive in the Games.
Fine.
Do your normal straight love story.
Bor-ing.
Oh, and, Seleca...
throw in a surprise twist at the end,
like she dies or something.
I like that.
Attention, contestants.
We have a rule change.
There can now be two winners of the Starving Games.
Great. So Marco and Peter
can team up to kill me.
Uh, specifically two people of different genders.
Oh.
Okay. Okay.
So I hook up with Marco,
and we kill Peter together.
Yes!
Yeah. I like that.
No, we were thinking more like you could team up with Peter.
No! No!
No, no, I, um...
I like the whole Marco idea better.
Hey, Kantmiss, do me a favor here,
and hook up with Peter. Please.
I could lose my job for this.
And that's my problem how?
Oh, hey.
Heh heh. Hey, guys. What's going on?
Nah, don't worry.
I got it under control. I swear.
W-What are you... What are you doing?
Um...
Ohh!
I thought we were friends.
Ah, thanks.
But I got us backstage passes to Justin Bieber.
Oh, my God.
No. No, no, don't you do it!
Right.
Um, I'm just gonna go team up with Peter now, so...
Hmm.
Peter, are you here?
I'm camouflaged.
Where are you?
I'm over here.
I don't see you.
I used my skills as a baker.
to seamlessly blend in to my surroundings.
Okay, well, can you give me a hint?
I'm in the cake.
Oh.
You're injured.
Marco found out that I really wasn't into him
and that I ultimately was protecting you.
And he did this to you?
No.
I just got my back waxed.
Aah!
Oh, that... that looks bad.
I mean, it's...
Oh. Aah!
Oh, it's really oozy. Ow. Okay.
Well, stop poking it!
Okay, well, we should take care of you
before the infection starts to take over.
Come on.
Ooh.
Aah!
Sorry.
Stop poking it, please.
Okay.
Ah, they're cute together
Yeah, well, I still want them to die.
Yeah. Duh!
Okay.
Marco won't find us in here. Come on.
I hope they get naked.
Come on!
Oh.
Night's falling. It's gonna get freezing.
You've got a fever.
Here. I'll check my bag
for something for warmth.
Thanks, Kantmiss.
A Snuggie!
Ah. Mmm.
So warm and comfy.
What? Huh?
You know...
I've had a crush on you for the longest time.
I used to follow you home from school every day.
Every day.
And I remember when you got
your first dress-up dolly on your eighth birthday.
And when you turned 12
and got your first period.
I watched you shower every night,
and after you got out,
I would pick through the drain and collect your hair.
What?
You made a hair doll of me?
Not just one.
Ohh.
That's you and me,
and those are our six kids.
And who's that?
That's our puppy, Alphie.
Woof woof!
Woof! Eww.
She's the runt of the litter,
but we love her all the same.
Ohh.
Ah, you got a hairy chick, dude.
I'm so hungry.
Poor baby.
Soup! What?
That'll definitely make you feel better.
Hmm?
What?
I...I think that they want us to be more romantic,
and, in return, they'll send us stuff to make you better.
Sounds good to me.
Sorry, Dale.
What?!
Really?
Ooh. Oh, come on.
Hey, who thinks they're gonna do it?
We do! We do!
Screw you all!
What is it now?
All right!
Peter, I don't know if I can do this.
Oh, my back.
I'm dying.
I don't know how much longer I can hang on.
All right. Let's...
give them what they want.
Fantastic.
True dat.
Ow. Ow!
Can you not grab my butt so hard?
I'm not touching your butt at all.
Ohh!
Do not be afraid.
I am but a kindly old wizard.
Get your hand off my ass!
Right. Well...
let me explain.
You see, we were traveling.
We were on...
We were on our way
to the Misty...
the Misty Mountains, yes.
And then we heard a moan
coming from inside this cave,
and fearing it to be a moan of distress
and being the good Samaritans that we are,
we came in here to help you.
Get out!
Yes. Well. Okay.
I bid you adieu.
Ooh. Ooh.
Whoa!
Yeah, love it! I love it! Yeah!
Not her first trip to the rodeo, eh?
Oh, yeah! Oh, Kantmiss!
Yeah! Oh!
Wow! Whoa.
Ohh! Ohh!
Oh, Peter, yes!
Score!
Even I don't get to do that!
Oh, give me your hand. Oh, God.
Yes!
Ride the donkey. Yes!
Ohh! Ohh!
And it's even better in 3-D.
Ooh. Ooh.
Thanks again for last night.
Now that you're better,
we have to go out there.
We have to kill Marco so we can both win the game and go home.
I...I would, but...
I think the infection's starting to come back.
Don't push it!
Where do you think you're going?
You can't go in there!
Whoa! Did you...Ha!
He's right there.
When are they gonna kill each other already?
I'm getting bored. Me, too.
Aah!
It's time to end this once and for all.
Siri.
Dang! What you need now?
Let's have a grand finale.
Send in the big guns.
Oh, shit.
I'll give you a war you wouldn't believe.
Hasta la vista, baby.
Yippie-ki-yay...
Oh.
Damn it. I don't have a catchphrase.
Ha ha ha! I have so many of them.
I'll be back.
You know what I mean, Chuck?
No.
Because I'm Chuck Norris,
and catchphrases need me!
Enh.
Why don't you shut up,
you smarty-pants wisenheimer piece of shit?!
Let's just kill 'em.
Oh.
Ready!
Aim.
Yes!
Yo, Adrian!
Fire!
Gah!
Dale?
What's going on with you and this guy?
I'll talk to you about it later.
I saw you kiss him.
I am in the middle of a death match.
Do you like him?
Dale, you are embarrassing me.
Go home. Nyah.
No! If anyone should leave...
he should.
Okay. Yeah. I-I'll leave.
Now, Dale! Fine.
Fine!
But I'm changing my Facebook status to single.
Sorry about that.
He's always been really clingy.
That's cool.
Unbelievable.
What are you gonna do, Kantmiss?
You shoot and miss, lover boy here is dead.
Yes!
No, no, no, no!
Huh? Huh?
Yeah.
Oh! Oh!
That'll work.
How about that, Cleaver?
Against all odds, they've done it. They've won.
Yay.
Whew!
Peter, we won.
We survived!
We're both going home.
Attention, contestants.
There has been yet another rule change.
And if you're thinking what I'm thinking,
you're right.
There again can be only one winner.
Good luck.
What if we don't give 'em the satisfaction?
What if we both kill ourselves
and there are no victors?
We'll ruin the Games,
and we'll show th-that the Capital,
they can't control us!
I found these poisonous berries in the woods.
W-We can eat them a-and die.
Shit ain't personal,
strictly business, ya dig?
Whaah! Whoa!
Fuck me!
Best Starving Games ever!
It's a nice shot, Kantmiss.
What're you doing here?
I practically show up
at the end of every movie.
Superhero movies, yeah, but...
Well, that's what I wanted to talk to you about.
We could use some fresh, young blood.
I mean, shit!
Just how many sequels to "Iron Man,"
"Thor" and "Captain America" can we make, right?
And you're pretty handy with that bow and arrow.
Ahem!
Uh, Nick, the, uh,
bow and arrow is sort of my thing.
Shut your ass, Hawkeye!
You're lucky you even in the Avengers!
Yeah, but... And don't you think
for one goddamn minute
that Marvel is gonna spin off your character!
"Hawkeye, colon,
The Avenger Nobody Gives a Shit About,"
will definitely not be coming soon to a theater near you!
Burn!
Burn.
Ow.
Oh, stop being such a cherry!
So what do you say, Kantmiss?
I'm in.
But, um, I'm kind of hungry.
Do you mind if we get something to eat first?
Let's go get some shawarma.
Avengers assemble!
Wait, don't step off those...
Oops.
Oh! You know what that sound means?
Bob's Post-Game Bloopers.
Aah! Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Good.
Blooper reel.
Ohh.
Sorry.
Blooper reel!
Cutting! Yeah!
Oh.
And the wig is down.
Okay. I'm sorry.
I gotta get more excited about you.
Let's do it.
Touch my leg.
Here we go.
Dude, stop.
Prank, take one.
Ohh!
Look at you!
Dale, that's romantic and all.
Yes, why don't you give me a little dance?
On the down, not the up.
That's good. Now like a penguin.
That's the worst penguin I've ever seen. Do it again.
Do you like watching Pygmies?
Oh, yeah. Oh. That looks good.
Look at that dripping.
I just got my back waxed.
I'm sorry.
Kick. Hah!
Sorry.
I kicked your ass.
No, that's fine. Don't...
And this is my sidekick.
Mother pus. What'd I say?
With me.
And this is...
Shh. ...my sidekick.
And this is my sidekick.
Yeah. That's funny. You got one line.
You do.
Ready?
And I have another Tess Tickles.
I need to see a bi...
No, it's not, "I need to see."
Stop hiding, and show me...
God damn it.
I need a pair of Tess Tickles!
Shit.
For bug zapper.
Contact.
Contact. Contact. Contact.
Uh-oh.
Hold on.
I'm sorry.
A partially eaten pickle.
So happy Starving Games,
and may the odds be never in your favor.
That is the worst pickle I've ever had.
We have to kill Marco and win the games.
Sorry. Ahh. Sorry.
We have to kill Marco so we can both go home
and win the ga... God damn it. Sorry.
Wow, that's amazing.
That is good. What is that?
It's a divine mixture
of fox blood and bear
Delicious. Right?
Hey!
Hey, Phil, stay down there
and put your finger in his mouth.
Okay. We're done.
We're done with this.
Blooper reel.
Cutting!
鸡饿游戏
♫ 我没抽到 ♫
♫ 我已年满18岁 ♫
♫ 对我来说不用再游戏 ♫
♫ 呜，认命吧 ♫
♫ 动起来，动起来 ♫
♫ 动起来，室内的人动起来 ♫
♫ 动起来，这是室内摇滚的时间 ♫
♫ 摇起来，摇起来 ♫
♫ 感受摇动，随着心情变化 ♫
♫ 圆圆，就像月亮满月 ♫
♫ 继续保持，那个地方烧起来 ♫
♫ 嗯，感觉舒畅 ♫
♫ 我喜欢它，令人惊叹 ♫
♫ 我们努力接球 ♫
♫ 舞会，所以它不能错过的 ♫
♫ 我的团队不会输的 ♫
♫ 放开，为您表演 ♫
♫ 动起来，动起来 ♫
♫ 动起来，这时候，晃动的房子吗 ♫
♫ 动起来，这时候，摇滚，摇滚，摇滚 ♫
♫ 动起来，这时候，摇滚，摇滚 ♫
♫ 呀，加油 ♫
♫ 哦！哦！哦！加油 ♫
♫ 拉，啦啦啦 ♫
♫ 请闭上你的眼睛 ♫
♫ 你的生活是流失 ♫
♫ 是的，你会死的 ♫
♫ 你的嘴会爬满蛆 ♫
♫ 可不可检查一下 ♫
♫ 蛆都跑出来了 ♫
♫ 巴拉巴拉 ♫
♫ 巴拉，巴拉 ♫
♫ 哦，宝贝 ♫
♫ 你知道吗，我们怎么办 ♫
♫ 这是做爱的时间 ♫
♫ 只有我和你 ♫
♫ 哦，宝贝 ♫
♫ 你知道，我们来到了什么办 ♫
♫ 喔，凯迷思，这是做爱的时间 ♫
♫ 只有我和你，喜欢吗 ♫
♫ 因为现在你在这里 ♫
♫ 我就要去了… ♫
♫ 哦，宝贝，呀 ♫
♫ 十二区！你知道我们要做什么 ♫
♫ 这就是它！这是做爱的时间 ♫
♫ 只有我和你，啊 ♫
♫ 哇哦，哇 ♫
♫ 动起来 ♫
♫ 动起来… ♫
♫ 动起来，室内的人动起来 ♫
♫ 室内的人动起来… ♫
♫ 室内的人动起来，动起来… ♫
♫ 动起来，室内的人动起来… ♫
♫ 蹦恰恰，蹦恰恰 ♫
♫ 没跟上节拍 ♫
♫ 蹦，恰，蹦，恰 ♫
♫ 室内的人动起来… ♫
♫ 室内的人动起来 ♫
♫ 动起来，现在是摇滚时间，摇滚，摇滚 ♫
♫ 动起来，室内的人动起来 ♫
♫ 动起来，现在是摇滚时间… ♫
♫ 动起来 ♫
♫ 动起来，现在是摇滚时间，摇滚，摇滚… ♫
♫ 动起来，动起来，动起来 ♫
♫ 动起来 ♫
嗨，凯迷思！
我的伟大，和强大的
啊哈！
呆恶！
只是想，给你个惊喜
你让我错失了我的猎物
嗷
狗杂种！我的背啊！
看看我得到了什么
那玩意是真的吗？
哦！想想看！
是块令人作呕的面包！
看着你
好吧
你知道…
我们可以离开这里
我们可以找到别的地方住
像在哪里？
任何地方，只要比这地方好就行
达尔富尔，叙利亚
纽泽西州
呆恶，那真的很浪漫并且…
但我没办法离开我的妹妹
我也不能离开
亲爱的年老奶奶等着我照顾她
天啊，我永远没有我自己的孩子
我的意思是你如何养育一个孩子
在这一个他监看着的地方
人间各种悲剧，然后转眼忘记
最为变态的一种娱乐
‘饥饿游戏’
成年礼和怀孕
早安
十二区的饥饿公民们
今天的新闻是，我们仍然没有食物
天气跟大便一样糟
哦，还有别忘了
今天是抽签仪式
因此各位家长请把你们心爱的孩子带来
广场，来一次死亡乐透
谢谢
我听说有些孩子，太害怕
被选上
所以试着采取一些丧失资格的手段
造成伤害或自残
那只是个传说吧
呃！
排好队
哦，别这样，贱人
因此事实
你的行动特权，已经没有了
回去排队
嗜血的家伙
哎，别说话
继续前进
我得去找我的妹妹
祝你好运
呸吐你，凯迷思
嘿，老妈
我好害怕，凯迷思，人家怕怕
嘿，嘿，不要怕，我给你带来这个
这是最勇敢的鸟，上面还有…
一只鸡
当你带着它，没什么不好的事会发生在你身上
嘘嘘，不，不要哭了
你会没事的，好吗
我保证
继续前进
排好队！
男左女右！
欢迎来到第75届，饥饿游戏
哦，哦！哦！
嘿，哦！
那是，我的香肠！
从我们尊敬的领袖传来一段视讯
屎落总统
他曾经杀死他的老母…
因为她忘了切掉三明治外面面包的皮
他唯一的脸书好朋友，是梅尔·吉布逊
他有一个自己的部落格
在上面泄漏电影的结局
上面没有声明‘狗仔警告’
什么，他就是…
世界上最可怕的人
我不是很喜欢啤酒的
但是如果我想要，我选择特雷斯·一块死
味道有点像尿一样
啊哈！
每一年，我都会让你们观看此视讯
因为，你都是傻瓜
人们忘记在过去
狗屎真的击中了风扇
组织太大了，并且人们开始失去信心
他们静坐罢工，聚众闹事
你选出女神卡卡作为总统
和她的竞选搭档，妮奇·米娜
这就是为什么我们穿，这些稀奇古怪的衣服吧
和怪异的发型
后来我接手
把国家分成各区域
所以那些愚蠢的行为，永远不会再发生
啊哈！
已经证明，民主没有用
在这里以我的第六感来看
保证所有的自由意志都不见
别再把那丑陋的头像放上去
是的，自从那后导致我们今天的情况
只是为了证明我是一个很屌的人
你们是如此无能为力
自从看过，阿弱的‘过关斩将’
和日本变态片‘大逃杀’
我想出了，饥饿游戏
从各地区挑选两个孩子
玩死亡游戏，只有一个幸存者
赢家能获得丰富奖金
包括一只老火腿…
哦，我超爱老火腿
凭此券到地铁速食店
购买任何东西可以打六折
和…
一个被吃过一部份的酸黄瓜
最后祝玩，饥饿游戏愉快
祝你永远好运
屎落总统出品
现在开始选出参加者！咳咳
休·借颗屎
嗯
不在吗，嗯，好的
我再重抽一个，嘿
肥鹅·穆特屎(谐音似塞满女性器官)
请上来肥鹅·穆特屎
叮·狗不累(音似性无能)
看看身后
四处找一下，叮·狗不累
这是全国直播！
你们不要笑的太早
当你们当中两个被抽出并丢进屠宰场
你就隔屁了
咳咳
没关系
呸吐你·艾薇秀逗
好喔！
太棒！太棒！
老娘没抽到
好喔！
呼！喔！呀！
喔！来吧！给我来个
嗯，再来一次，哦！噢
但是我被选中
呸吐你，我很抱歉
呸吐你，不，这不公平
不要给我可怜小狗的眼神
我自愿！
哦
我自愿参加饥饿游戏！
谢谢，我的大姐姐啊
哦！如果你不能活着回来
我可以吃掉您的宠物仓鼠吗？
什么
来吧，亲爱的
现在，让我们挑一个男孩加入你的队伍
我也自愿！
谁说的
是我
我是彼得·马拉鸡
哦
嘿，凯迷思
我自告奋勇，因为我喜欢你
非常喜欢，我很抱歉
我认识你吗
嗯…
我，我是面包师的儿子
有一次，你饿的时候我给你面包
哦，我想起
你给我一个核桃面包
嗯
对啊
老娘对坚果严重过敏
我差点死了
让我们的参赛者发言！
而且不要忘了转台看，饥饿游戏
唐顿修道院，影集终后就是
我们不能说再见吗
当然可以，亲爱的
中央政府还是有点人性的
你有9秒的时间
呸吐你！凯迷思！
不要担心，你跟妈妈在一起就可以放心了
不知彼得到底在想什么
什么
我的意思是，他像一个白痴对不对
你觉得他能帮什么忙吗
呃…
时间到了！
呆恶！是吗
答应我，你会照顾呸吐你！
我会的，凯迷思
我保证
等一下！
待会见
脑残
耐吉的标志
是的，我开始在
我的脸上卖广告空间
你愿意卖自己，跟妓女一样
是我让你当上头不程式员的主要因素
谢谢你，总统先生
我们的大电视节目秀怎样了
太棒了，爱吸顿·酷鸡取代叉你辛
没有人在意给份狗屎的
饥饿游戏
那将是一个超棒的演出
我们有一些，非常有趣的参赛者
12区有2名自愿者
自愿者
笑得我尿失禁
因为你把它制订成法律
说如果有谁不看竞赛的话会被公开打鞭
我们期待，创高收视率
经过去年的当机
我真的别无选择
名人一起饥饿游戏，是一个很烂的主意
没有人会参加的
因为欧普拉会吃掉其他选手
我希望这个游戏结束能功德圆满
我不想，有一些败笔
从一个贫穷的地区，参加游戏，并煽动群众
她的射箭技能，和她的黑色的头发
辫子塑造成一个注册商标
鼓舞人心的反抗，不仅将颠覆我的统治
同样也产生一个成功的
重量级的反动炸弹
哦！
我可能需要，一个新的园丁
我是尸躺立·西舍曼，这里是
饥饿游戏，前秀，!
明天，游戏就要开始
但今晚，我们要与参赛者会面
你会一个个认识他们
听听背后感人的故事
我们会使用大量编辑过的
家庭录影带，悲惨的见证来感动你们
当你们开始对他们有所感动
我们会把他们送去恐怖的大屠杀
让我们见一下我们第一个参赛者
按照区域从第一个区开始
他很有希望能赢得这场比赛
他是金发细腰的
他是年轻的雅利安人的化身
他就是马哥！
呀！
啊啊！呀！
你好，帅哥
和我们谈谈你自己
我来自一区，这是一个主要的区
你是谁
我是辛纳蒙
你的发型师
你还行吗
我很害怕
我不想死
啊，我来告诉你
我相信你
你能赢
我看过你的记录
你比他们都要聪明和狡猾
真的吗你觉得，我会赢吗
是的，帕特丽夏
我就知道
谁是帕特丽夏
你不是从三区来的女孩
不，我来至十二区
你知道，这完全正常的
你看起来很坚强
现在从12区来的彼得，马拉鸡
彼得和我们聊一聊
在你生命中有没有比较特别的人呢
嗯
是有一个
是啊，跟我们说说
哦
好吧，告诉我们
那人也在现场
那人同样…
也在游戏里吗
在游戏跟你再一起吗
噢哇，噢哇
那继续
怎么讲…
他是我一直在等候的人
可以多相处的
你这狗杂种
所以…
身材高大
美丽的大眼睛
身材火辣的冒烟，但是…
你知道吗，比什么都重要的是
这个人有很多的爱心
噢哇，噢哇
好吧，你一定要告诉我们是谁呢
他就是马哥！
我吗
嘿
咦，咦
让我们以掌声谢谢彼得
你这个小混蛋！
我会一脚踩爆你的小菊花！
哦！哎呀
你说的是怎么一回事呢
这就是所谓的，建立联盟
你没看过‘幸存者’，或‘老大哥’
啊哈！什么
你最近什么时候修剪你的脚趾甲
哦
现在请我们最后的参赛者
从十二区来的
凯迷思·艾薇秀逗
喔！
让我们来看看
凯迷思是世界上最好的大姐姐
她照顾我，她养我，给我衣服
她读书给我听
自从爸爸去世后
妈妈变得神智不清
但是并不阻止，我们三个寻找快乐
从第一次，我看到凯迷思，我就知道
我就知道她是我生命中的那个人
她不得了
她是一个真正的淑女
哦，天啊
哦！哦，我的天啊
哦！哦！
是不是，刚刚很感人
噢哇，噢哇
让我们请她出来好吗
凯迷思·艾薇秀逗！
凯迷思，这礼服真是漂亮
给我们一点旋转
嘿，继续
不要害羞
非常好
哦
哇，我听懂了是点火
旋转礼服会烧起来
火焰
哦！哦！
哦，我的天啊，哦
哦，啊哈！
你们为什么还在鼓掌，你们这些笨蛋
啊哈！
我烧起来了！我烧起来了！
让我们谢谢凯迷思，火焰的女孩！
啊！着火了！
着火了！它烧起来了！
我烧起来了！
早安，体育粉丝们
欢迎来到75届，饥饿游戏
我是主持人鲍伯·嗨洛克
与我的搭档
毒舌评论员，克利弗·威廉姆斯(大砍刀)
砍刀，你好
今天的比赛感到兴奋吗
太棒了
克利弗是过去游戏的赢家
事实上砍刀你为什么不告诉大家
在各区观看得大家
你是怎么得到，那可爱的的绰号
我用砍刀，杀掉每一人
仍然宝刀未老
你好，西丽
你好，萨乐卡
最近好吗
不怎好
不错
好的，看来参赛者
已经到现场了
西丽，镜头切换到现场
祷告吧，小子，因为你已经死了
倒数开始
30…
29…
哦，天啊，28…
27…
嗯
26…
25…
24…
23…
21…
现在这点是非常重要的
要求参赛者，不要动
数到零之前银圈不会关闭
否则会被蹦，蹦
场上装满炸药
不需要提醒我
我偷跑太早，以至现在不能嗯嗯与拉拉
看看示范
13…
12…
11…咦
你们在这里干什么
我们被邀请来的
举行开幕仪式
这就是屠宰场
哦，你应该找第二现场
哦，谢谢，谢谢
哎呀，不错
哇！这是什么方法，开始游戏！
10…
9…
8…
7…
6…
5…
4…
3…
2…
1…
西丽，更血腥些
哦
这样好多
哦！哦！
是马哥！呀！
放手！
我先来的！
啊！现在把它给我！
我不会轻易放手的
你背后中镖！
我没事！
什么
没事
这样没事，你不放手
我要这个背包！
我要它，它是我的！
我不会轻易放手！
那是我的背包！
那是什么声音
大炮的声音，他们发射的
每当有人死了，他们就发射一发
很好，看来我的胜算
对我来说多一些
我的蛋蛋！
哦！看来很痛
让我们来看看慢动作重播
我的蛋蛋！
我的蛋蛋
我的蛋蛋，我，我的蛋
我的蛋
我的蛋！
这样会让我起笑，鲍伯
离我远点！
哇！
这个女孩是谁
她来自什么区
我站在杂碎的十二区
那里的人们，不敢相信，彼得和凯迷思的
可以存活过开幕式
你可以看到大家都兴奋高亢
很长一段时间这个区域都没有赢过
呀！啊！
加油，凯迷思！喔！
这是我的马子！
呀！
转回转播台
我上电视了！
谢谢，尸躺立
现在比数如何，砍刀
很多人已死
尽管如此，还有很多人活着
让我突然眼睛一亮
哦，看来凯迷思的以他的方式
来到屠宰场的边缘
西丽，让她慢下来
噢
现在，让我们的凯迷思，回到场中央
呼啦！
释放惊心动魄的音效
哦
嗯
你想要玩玩那就来
西丽
耶，你需要什么
以最新的攻击她
用我们最先进武器
喔，哈！
噢，该死！
呀！嘻嘻！
嘻嘻！
不
怎么怎么
很高兴看到我柳丁吗
嘿，嘿，嘿！
当你以一个黄色眼神你会得到什么
昆汀·塔沦落(色情片导演)
‘色情小说’你会得到什么呢
果浆
嘿，凯迷思
我最后一次见到小笼包
是我看到一对金橘的时候
啊哈！
加油，凯迷思！
哦
她肯定会说‘哟’对不起踢爆你屁股！
你，你，闭嘴，西丽，你闭嘴！
妈的，不要恨，玩家
你，恨这游戏！
哇！我从来没有见过，有人这样做
她坏蛋
我顶
让我想起了跟自己一点点像
在我有过多的情绪前，我要停下来
尝尝老娘的屁！
你认为你很神勇吗
看看你能不能搞定这，贱人！
嘿，朋友们，加油！我们走这条路！
来吧，快点！
走吧！
当我发现她的时候，她就是我的
她肯定在这里的某个地方
你确定凯迷思，走这条路
嗯，我知道
你怎么能这么肯定，我们可以信任你吗
我的意思是，你是自愿参加这游戏的
只是为了接近凯迷思的
不
我的意思是，也许一开始是
但我不再喜欢她了
真的吗
嗯，你知道
早在12区时
她的作为相当是妓女
啊
她在那里
嘿
做得好，彼得
谢谢
我会打爆她的肠子
这个小公主，全部是我的
啊！
凯迷思在那！
哦，我们会杀了你
在我们吃，我们的美味佳肴
咦
你怎么能，与他们搅和在一起
我不知道
我…
真的很喜欢他们
他们太酷了，而广受欢迎
我的意思是，我是高中的艾薇俱乐部
我从来没有机会与痞子们一起玩
嗯，跟我们在一起
太好了
嗯，哦
嘿，他们说，他们希望，跟我一起去舞会
我们要去租一辆豪华轿车，和一切东西
是不是真棒
彼得，他们只是利用你
在饥饿游戏只能有一个赢家
好的
很好，凯迷思，游戏就要结束
格老木，你上
喔呼呼！
哦！看样子这里有一个溜鸟侠
每一场比赛都会发生
鬼叫，雅虎
快滚，贱人，快滚！
回来，回来
给我…
刺得好，嗯
他这样投
然后，它这样回
事实上，砍刀
今天绝对是
屠宰日！
屠宰日，屠宰日！
自由屠宰日
赌命保险赞助播出
因为生命是宝贵的…
赌命，赌命
我们要怎样玩死她
咳咳
呃…
为什么不要我们先离开
嗯，去杀死，其他一些孩子
稍后再回来吗
我们会等着你的
她迟早会下来的
太恶了
嘿
嘘
哦
有蜂巢砸在他们的头上
好吧，嘘，嘘
这些都是守卫兵蜂
被叮到会产生严重的幻觉
或隔屁
哦！
嗷！嗷！
哦！我的屁股！啊！
我想我刚刚吞下一只！
哇
哦
哇，哦
什么
哦，我的天哦！
哦，哦
喔
哦
不会吧
两道彩虹
呜！
两道彩虹！哈！
哦
它开始看起来
像四道彩虹！
哦，我的…天啊！
没错！没错！
啊哈哈！
哦，彩虹的味道
哦
哦，哦
哦，哇
哦，我的
那是…
哦
不要有突然的大动作
怎么了
我从来没有，看过这情况发生
它们是什么
灵魂保护者
灵魂保护者！
啊！哦，我的天！搞定他们！搞定他们！
搞定他们！搞定他们！
你们别想，带走我的灵魂！
哦！为什么呢
你头顶有一个
不，不，不，不
噢
我觉得，我全部搞定他们
灵魂保护者持有，所有我们古老的祖先亡灵
那是我妹妹
我的奶奶
和我喝醉的希拉阿姨
哎呀
你是谁
我们是一个值得骄傲的古代人
由詹姆斯·卡麦隆创建
我是世界之王！
看这里
给我你的发辫
把尾端联结一起就可做爱
纳美人的格调
好啊
哦
嗯
哦，是的
凯迷思
凯迷思！
是
凯迷思！凯迷思！
凯迷思！
难道你想跟我交配
什么没有！
不，不，不，不，嗯…
我认为我，只是产生幻觉
你最好不要，我只有12岁(未成年)
依我所见，如果我们要生存
我们应该协力工作
万一我们都活到最后
我会毫不犹豫
在这场比赛，杀人或被杀
我会不考虑杀了你
杀死了，完美的结尾
妈的不就是个人
买卖就是买卖，你懂吗
好吧，我也是这么想的
我可以生一堆火
把马哥，和他的同志引到空地
如果你发现弓和箭
你就可以解决他们
是的这是个伟大的想法
马哥绝对想不到
喂
我就在这里
快跑！快跑！
抓住她！
妈的
最后会寡不敌众
我该怎么办，我该怎么办
仔细想想，凯迷思，仔细想想
痔疮的重击
迅速重踢他的后庭，使他痛不欲生
重击！
低晃的蛋蛋，爆破它
用最简单出击打球
矬蛋的金属牙齿矫正器
抓起橡皮筋，反弹头骨
严重的痘痘
嗯
专用外用粉刺霜膏
精虫充脑的宅男孩
运用天然木兰飞弹解决
让你来划一下
你太辣了
重击！
嘻
你准备好去死吗
这不是真的！
我的意思是，还有一线希望
我能坚持撑到续集
咦，咦
嗯！
好吧！我们知道那哨音表示什么
中场休息
啊，太可惜
我想看她被杀
中场休息
饥饿游戏，拉拉队出场
威尔刚赞助播出
嗯，我喜欢它，西丽，但它不是
它不是激凸舞
别担心，嘘，我成全你
更情色，更激凸来了
凯迷思，上半场很惊险
请告诉我们，你现在想什么
首先，我想，感谢我的主，救世主耶稣基督
嗯，我想，如何获胜，尸躺立
我只想赢得比赛
鲍伯
尸躺立你听懂了，凯迷思的意思了吗
已意识到她创造的狂热吗
我不这么认为，鲍伯
她很激励人心的
砍刀中场精彩毒舌
啊哈！
看一看，什么趋势，现在推特上剖
海伦在七区的呼叫‘凯迷思给我希望！’
和汤玛斯，在十一区写道
‘摇滚凯迷思，你辣爆了！’
泰隆在康普顿区呼叫
‘哟，凯迷思，是一颗大炸弹’
她将吹起热潮！
笑脸表情符号
她太红了
并且我也有机会
在凯迷思专区
其中疯凯迷思是同时间有最高人气！
我现在12区
每个人都疯了
这是最终血拼灰姑娘的故事
这里的人们就吃这一套
购买任何一切有关商品指南
凯迷思，或饥饿的游戏有关
T恤，马克杯
手提包，杯套
公仔
看我，我就像凯迷思
哦！
我的球
不错！直接命中！
我要再射一次
哎！奶酪卷饼！
哦，那感觉很爽
这是一场势均力敌的，嗯
我差一点宰了你
我知道了，我当时想‘哦’
保持先前的姿势
游戏继续！
耶！
你准备受死
啊哈！啊哈！
你这个小杂种！
嘿！
啊哈！
鲁迪
给我唱催眠曲
好吧
不是你！
她来！
我要死了
不，不，不会的
当然，你不会死的
蛆是不是，有点戏剧性的
该死的，泰勒·斯威夫特
太感动了…
已隔屁了，砍刀
这使我的眼球落下
如果我的泪腺，没有撕裂
哦，哦
对不起
这太扯了
中央不能对待我们像蚂蚁一样
呀！呀！
我们的生命是我们自己的
他们不能让我们互相残杀
为了他们病态的娱乐！
呀！呀！
你们怎么说呢
让我们起身对抗
并推翻这个，极权政府
一劳永逸！
呀！呀！
喔呼！
我们采取半磅，A级牛肉…
放上奶酪
然后，我们最重要的辣椒…
一个热狗和排骨
低热量的沙拉酱覆盖上面
然后我们最重要的一片，辣香肠比萨饼
芝麻的甜面包夹上
嗯，嗯
嘿，呃…
我们仍然，要去对抗
也许以后吧
我太饿了
然后，我们添加，沙茶酱…
番茄，洋葱和生菜
然后，我们添加了猪肉培根
洋葱圈，花耶菜，玉米奶酪
罐头肉酱和鸡翅膀…
烤火腿，猪肠
不要忘了，西瓜切片
加上两勺，开心果冰淇淋
并完成家最后一个芝麻面包
600000卡路里，三层大汉堡
星巴克的
免费的拿铁
凯迷思发烧，造成，一个严重的问题
我们差一点引起骚动
我们应该做什么呢
给他们更多
我听不懂
饥饿游戏，正在火热
只要看看报导
我们终于可以，赢得一座艾美奖
但节目缺少，一个重要的因素
什么，每一个成功的表演都需要什么
把它推到一个更新的层次
我已知道，你是什么意思
一个爱情故事！一个女同性恋的爱情故事！
等一下，拉拉的爱情故事
谁不喜欢看，两个小妞搞在一起
我知道，这时候我会很喜欢的
但在这游戏其他女生
都隔屁了，没有其他活着
好吧
那就弄个正常的爱情故事
太给他…无聊了
哦，还有，萨乐卡…
结束时，扔一个惊喜剧情
像她死掉或某事
我喜欢这样
注意，参赛者
我们改变一个规则
在这游戏，现在可以有两位获胜者
太好了，因此，马哥和彼得
可以组队杀了我
嗯，特别是两个人，不同的性别
哦
好吧，不错
所以我要去钓马哥
我们一起杀了彼得
没错！
嗯，我喜欢这样
不，我们想让你与你与彼得组队
不！不！
不，不，我，嗯
我喜欢跟马哥的想法更好
嘿，凯迷思，帮帮忙好吗
去钓彼得吧
不然我会没工作的
现在变成我的问题了
哦，嘿嘿
嘿嘿，嘿，兄弟这是怎么回事呢
不，不用担心
它在我的控制之下，我发誓
你在…你在做什么
嗯…
哦！
我还以为我们是朋友
啊，谢谢
我找到通往贾斯汀·比伯捷径的通行证
哦，我的天啊
不，不，你不能答应！
好吧
嗯，现在我要去跟彼得组队去了，所以…
嗯
彼得，你在这里吗
我有伪装的
你在哪里
我在这里
我没有看到你
我用技能变成了面包师
非常符合这种环境
好吧，你能不能给我一个提示吗
我在蛋糕里
哦
你受伤了吗
马哥发现我布是真心跟他
我最终是在保护你
这是他做的吗
不要
我给我的背部上蜡
啊哈！
哦，那，看起来不太好
我的意思是，这是…
哦，啊哈！
哦，这真的太恶心，噢，好吧
好吧，别再戳了！
好吧，我应该，好好照顾你的
在发病前，搞定它
来吧
哦
啊哈！
抱歉
请别戳了
好吧
啊，他们在一起，还蛮可爱
是啊，好了，我还是，希望看到他们死
嗯，咄！
好吧
来吧，在这里马哥不会找到我们的
我想看到他们脱光
来吧！
哦
晚上温度下降，会冻死人的
你发烧了
我检查我的包包
看有没有取暖的东西
谢谢，凯迷思
毛毯衣！
嗯，嗯
温暖又舒服
什么，咦
你知道…
我暗恋你很久了
每天放学，我曾经跟着你回家
每天
我还记得，当你
八岁生日拿到第一件有穿衣服的洋娃娃
而当你十二岁时
你的第一个MC来了
每天晚上我看着你洗澡
洗后
我会在排水口收集你的头发
什么
你给我做一毛公仔呢
不只一个
哦
这是你和我
而这些都是我们的六个孩子
那是谁
这就是我们的小狗，阿飞
汪汪！
汪！恶
她是里面最小的
但我们爱她，都是一样的
哦
啊，你有一个毛茸茸的小妞
我太饿了
可怜的宝贝
这是什么，浓汤！
肯定，让你感到更好
嗯
这是什么
我想他们要我们，更浪漫一些
并且作为回报，他们会送，我们的一些东西，让你好更快
听起来不错
对不起，呆恶
什么
真的吗
哦，哦，来吧
嘿，谁认为，他们会搞起来呢
我们要看！我们要看！
太贼了你们！
现在要干吗(纸条:快表演精彩的)
这是对的！
彼得，我不知道我能不能做到这一点
哦，我的背部
我快要死了
我不知道我能坚持下去多久
好的，让我们…
给他们想要的
太棒了
同感
噢，嗷！
你不能用力捏我的屁股
我没有捏你的屁股
哦！
不要害怕
我只是，一位慈祥的老巫师
把手移开我的屁股！
好吧，嗯…
让我解释一下
你看，我们正在旅行
我们
我们要去的方向
迷雾
迷雾山，是的
我们听到了呻吟声
来自，这个洞穴里面
担心这是惨叫的呻吟
做为好心的矮人
我们来到这里，帮助你
滚出去！
是的，好的，好的
哪掰掰了
哦，哦
哇！
是啊，爱它！我喜欢它！呀！
不是她的第一次吧
哦，耶！哦，凯迷思！
呀！哦！
哇！哇
哦！哦！
噢，彼得，太好了！
厉害！
甚至我都没办法做这招！
哦，给我你的手，哦，天啊
没错！
老汉推车，没错！
哦！哦！
看3D更爽
哦，哦
昨晚，再次感谢
现在你好多了
我们必须出发
我们必须杀了马哥，我们就可以双赢和回家
我，我会的，但…
我认为又发病了
不要摸它！
你想要去哪里
你不能进去！
哇！你…哈！
他在那里的
他们什么时候会互相残杀吗
我觉得越来越无聊，我也一样
啊哈！
是该结束了，一劳永逸了
西丽
当！你现在需要什么
给我们压轴
送上大枪
哦，屎蛋
我会给你一个想像不到的战争
后会有期，宝贝
我一定会回来的
哦
该死的，我都没有一句名言
哈哈哈！我有很多
我会回来的
你知道我的意思吧，查克
不知
因为我，查克·诺里斯
名言需要我！
嗯
你们为什么不闭嘴
你们一群自以为聪明的狗屎
让我们杀了他们
哦
准备好了！
瞄准
好的！
哟，安德烈！
开火！
巴拉，巴拉！
呆恶
你这家伙，这是怎么回事呢
我待会再告诉你
我看到你亲他
我在死亡比赛中
你喜欢他吗
呆恶，你让我很尴尬
回家，喏
不！如果有人应该离开…
应该是他
好吧，嗯，我，我离开
现在，呆恶！好吧
好吧！
现在我要把我的脸书改成单身
我们对此深感抱歉
他总是黏巴达
这很酷的
令人难以置信
你现在要怎么办，凯迷思
你射歪，情人小狼狗就会隔屁
没错！
不，不，不，不！
咦，咦
耶
哦！哦！
这真的有用
怎么样，砍刀
排除万难他们已经做到了，他们已经赢了
耶
呼！
彼得，我们赢了
我们活下来了！
我们要回家了
注意，参赛者
规则又有改变
如果你想，我在想什么
你猜对了
规则又改回，只能有一个胜利者
祝你们好运
如果，我们不让他们称心如意呢
如果我们都自杀
就没有胜利者
我们就毁了游戏
我们会告诉中央
他们无法控制我们！
在树林中我发现这些，有毒的果实
我们可以吃了一起死
妈的这不个人问题
买卖归买卖，你了解吗
哇！呼！
我操！
饥饿游戏永垂不朽！
那一箭射得真好，凯迷思
你们是干什么，在这里干么
我几乎露脸
在每部电影结束时
超级英雄电影，没错，但
嗯，这是我想要和你谈谈的
我们可以使用，一些新鲜年轻的生力军
我的意思是，该死！
究竟有多少续集‘钢铁人’
‘雷神’和‘美国队长’我们可以做，对不对
你弓箭玩的不错
咳咳！
嗯，尼克，嗯
弓和箭，是我的专业
闭上你的屁眼，鹰眼！
你能在复仇者联盟，你就很幸运！
但是，而且你不觉得
就是一分钟
电影公司，也会把你这人物给删了！
‘鹰眼’结肠癌，隔了
‘复仇者联盟’不会关心一堆狗屎的
肯定不会受你不出现的威胁！
燃烧吧！
烧录
哦
别叽叽歪歪了！
所以你认为怎样，凯迷思
我加入
但是，嗯，我有点饿了
你不介意，我们先去找吃的东西吗
让我们去弄一些，沙威玛烤肉
复仇者联盟集合！
等一下，不要踩到那些机关
哎呀
哦！你知道吗，那声音意味着什么
鲍伯的片后NG片段
啊哈！哇，哇，哇
好
搞笑片段
哦
抱歉
搞笑片段！
切！呀！
哦
假发要掉了
好吧，对不起
我得比你更兴奋
让我们开始
摸我的大腿
好了，我们走吧
呆恶，别来
恶作剧，来一个
哦！
看看你！
呆恶，这真是浪漫
是的，你为什么不跳一下舞吗
再来一次
很好，现在看起来像一只企鹅
这是我见过最糟糕的企鹅，再来一次
你喜欢看矮人吗
哦，是的，哦，这看起来不错
看看汗留下来
我刚在我的背部上蜡
对不起
踢，哈！
抱歉
我踢到你的屁股
不，没关系，没事…
这，是我的好火鸡
姥姥不爱，我刚刚说了什么
和我
这是…
嘘，我的好火鸡
这是我的好火鸡
嗯，那很滑稽，你脸上有一条线
你开始
准备好了吗
而且我有另一个台词，踢死
我需要看到一个双向的台词，踢死
不，它不是‘我要看的’
别隐藏了出来吧
他妈的
我需要一对的台词，踢死！
妈的
捕蚊器
摸一摸
摸一摸，摸一摸，摸一摸
噢噢
等一下
对不起
吃了一部分的酸黄瓜
饥饿游戏，玩的快乐
也祝你们好运
这是我吃过最烂的酸黄瓜
我们必须杀马哥，并赢得比赛
抱歉，啊，抱歉
我们必须杀马哥，然后我们可以回家
赢得比…他妈的，抱歉
哇，太不可思议
吃起来不错，那是什么
这是一个神圣的混合物
狐狸和熊的血
很好吃吧，对吗
嘿！
嘿，肥鹅，待在那里
把你的手指头，放到他的嘴里去
好吧，我们就大功告成了
就玩到这里
搞笑片段
停！
字
字幕
字幕制
字幕制作
字幕制作 ★
字幕制作 ★ 至
字幕制作 ★ 至宏
字幕制作 ★ 至宏上
字幕制作 ★ 至宏上人